Even though it takes some time, I can imagine so it can stand there.
So now it is.
Quite so cleaned here again anyway.
But yes, it was an experience you can say.
Now I have difficult cleaning mania so I have said you can clean up after you.
Now I mean some cleaning.
This one needs to be lubricated with a little 5:56.
But now we should at least go and fix the horses.
We will take a walk with all the horses.
Oh no, it's hugs.
Oh a thousand wonders if it is possible to climb the hill without getting stilts?
We may try.
Yes I understand it.
But I now make chicken.
I can't decide if there is enough chicken, but I
Think so.
So it will be chicken, rice and so I will make my own sauce that is very, very
Tasty.
It is
creme fraiche and chili sauce.
Then if you want.
If you feel like this that you don't like creme fraiche then there is also
bearnaise sauce and it may not be the best combo in the world, but it is still a
But you are gratefully measured.
But you are not like when you eat type tacos and are measured for four days.
So it's done.
I think I pour on a little more chicken.
This is rose chicken
As we have received from my brother -in -law.
To test.
This is frozen because I want to hectare Robin's tractor pan because then could
You have let it stand and put it so there will be heat from above too, but I did not get
Borrow it.
So now this will be.
Oh what it boils here so
I season with salt, garlic and pepper.
There are three spices I like very much myself.
It is important to spice up what you like.
Then I also like chili, but I think we're not going to
Konstra to it too much.
And now I came up with one thing.
She was allergic to nuts.
Now we have no nuts here, but
May be good to keep track of one of the girls to not tolerate nuts.
But otherwise.
Yes.
We meat here.
So now we are starting to show up here.
It is still very cozy when you can do and usually we always take our food
in the kitchen.
It's not that it's super long here but it will be.
So the food is getting ready anyway.
Which feels good.
I have never really tasted them.
Oh, it tastes like a mixture of probably the Red and the Blue.
I'm probably just taste the red, but very cute.
I rarely drink energy drinks, but thank you very much prime mmmm.
Yes can drink a little neighbor or so.
Give it to someone I know likes Prime very much.
But I think it's fun to get these stuff because it's fun to test new
things.
But then I don't drink very much.
Or not at all energy drinks because i don't think it is i experience when
I myself drink energy drinks that I become very good then of course.
Sadly without him.
But that's it.
I'll go into Haley's room and twist one thing.
After all, I've been the world's opponent of snail mucus.
Think it's so disgusting.
So just the thought of scratching killer snails in the face of myself getting
me to want to start crying.
Type.
Now I say hello.
Ah but then I get a psychic
This then we have Hailey's solution to all the world's concerns and that is that
Throw everything in and of itself.
Maybe I should take on, but you see here, I panic.
However, I think I might be able to take on a bit of that it looks like it does on
her room because i called her ba can you go out to chloe and hang out with
Her and then I think she released everything and went.
But this is no exception and something she uses right on
Took too much.
It is such pads makeup pads and that is because she.
So really, I will buy this.
So to really lose it.
And that's because she.